Alright
In this lesson, we'll cover the types of wake-up words
and select them as configuration options
Previously, in this section
we would directly instantiate it here
This instantiation is quite low-level, right?
We definitely shouldn't do it this way here
So, how should we approach it?
We'll use a configuration method
When we write this configuration, it's similar to writing that protocol.
That is, the part about the protocol is the same.
We put it in the KCONFIG.
Copy this over.
When it comes to configuration, there are two types.
The types of wake-up methods.
There are two default methods, one of which uses the wake-up word approach.
And there are wake-up words in here.
There's also command word detection.
Use the wake-up method
After we have set up the configuration
We will proceed here
We can configure it
Let's configure it now
IDF point p y menu configure
When we define it here
We can use macros for conditional compilation
I see the same board level here
Here, let's configure the placeholder words.
We can choose this placeholder along with the command words.
Let's stick with the default placeholder for now.
Change it once.
Then, let's save it.
Let's check if there's a configuration here.
There should be a wake-up word configuration.
Now, let's search for it.
By the type of wake-up word.
Just search for this one.
We're currently using the wake word, right?
There's also this command word method.
We haven't set it up yet.
Is our current setup like this?
Then we can use conditional compilation.
It's the same as before here.
Our previous agreement was also through conditional compilation, right?
So now we'll use conditional compilation here as well.
If this is defined, right?
Let's make a copy of this.
And modify this, if this is defined.
Then add this header file.
And then,
Similarly, we do the same for the other one,
We also put it here.
And then, for this one, we are going to
This is it, right?
If it's not defined yet, right?
The command word hasn't been defined, right?
If we define the command word,
It would look like this.
Then, we can copy these two over as well,
And place them here for conditional compilation.
Similarly, when we create and instantiate here,
We do it this way here,
Then we put this inside here.
If it's this one
then we instantiate it this way
if it's the wake word
we instantiate it through the wake word
in this case
we use the trigger word method
to instantiate it
it will always be instantiated
Now we're using placeholders, right?
So that means
we don't need to worry about which one to use, right?
We compile it in through this configuration method.
Then, everything here is the same.
There's no difference here.
Everything we use is the same.
Then we'll do a bit of
And this part here
What we need to do is work on the welcome message here.
We should replace the placeholder word in this part.
When we print this out, we need to make sure that
we take a look at
the command words.
The welcome message is also included.
In the command words section,
we can't print this out in the same way.
Because we might not have configured this.
So let's remove the unconfigured model.
If we haven't configured the model,
we don't need to print it like this.
Let's delete this.
Then add a line here.
This is what we configure if we do.
We use command words to wake it up.
We must configure the model, right?
If this name doesn't exist,
it means the model hasn't been configured.
In this case, we'll just return
and print
Please configure the minutes model.
Otherwise, we'll print its model name like this.
The wake word also follows the same approach.
We need to make a check for it as well.
For the wake word,
You also need to set up a configuration
for the wake word
if it’s not configured, it will be the same
we’ll place this in the
initialization section
right after this
if the list is empty
if it equals zero
it means the wake word hasn’t been configured
Please configure the wake word as well.
Let's set it up like this.
And that’s all you need to do.
This way,
we have two methods for the wake-up function.
By using conditional compilation,
we can configure it through conditional compilation later on,
you can use either method,
we are currently using the wake word method.
So, let's configure it here.
We need to set up this model.
The wake word we're using now.
We need to configure the wake word.
Let's change the wake word.
Let's set it up.
Right here.
First, we need to turn off the previous model.
Then, let's find a wake word here.
Let's just pick one at random.
This one is available for commercial use.
H-Lexing is available for commercial use.
This one is also available for commercial use.
Let's go with this one.
We'll use this one for now.
If you want to customize it,
you can use the custom option.
by using the command method.
Then, we also need to configure this, right?
And configure the wake-up type, correct?
We configured it previously, right here, didn't we?
We are now doing wake-word detection.
It has already been configured.
Then we exit.
Now we can proceed with the compilation.
Just download it.
It's implemented.
I won't download this one.
Just this spot.
Of course, this is how we are testing it right now.
But the writing style for this part is like this.
Exactly.
This is the correct way to write it.
We are still working with the test code here.
We will organize and integrate the audio input later.
How to send it to the backend, right?
We will refine the entire process.
Alright, that's it for this lesson.